<?xml version="1.0"?>
<x:movies xmlns:x="urn:movies">
<Movie>
    <head> <!--x14116251--> </head>
    <bags>
        <h1>content</h1>
      <h2>year2015<h2>
<film11>
      <Film>Two by Two</Film>
      <Date> 1st May 2015</Date>
	  <actor>Ava Connolly,  Callum Maloney,  Dermot Magennis,  Tara Flynn</actor>
   </film11>

   <film12>
      <Film>Hunger games part:2</Film>
      <Date> 20th November 2015</Date>
	  <actor> Jennifer Lawrence, Josh Hutcherson, Liam Hemsworth</actor>
	  <about>As the war of Panem escalates to the destruction of other districts by the Capitol, Katniss Everdeen, the 
	  reluctant leader of the rebellion, must bring together an army against President Snow, while all she holds dear hangs in the balance.</about>
   </film12>
 
 <film13>
      <Film>Krampus (2015)</Film>
      <Date> 4th december 2015</Date>
	  <actor>  Adam Scott, Toni Collette, David Koechner, Allison Tolman</actor>
	  <about>A boy who has a bad Christmas ends up accidentally summoning a Christmas demon to his family home. </about>
   </film13>
   
   <film14>
      <Film>Chi-Raq (2015)</Film>
      <Date> 4th december 2015</Date>
	  <actor> Nick Cannon, Teyonah Parris, Wesley Snipes, Angela Bassett</actor>
	  <about>A modern day adaptation of the ancient Greek play Lysistrata by Aristophanes, set against the backdrop of gang violence in Chicago.</about>
   </film14>
  
   
   
   <h2>year2014</h2>
   <film15>
      <Film>The Letters (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 20th May 2014</Date>
	  <actor> Juliet Stevenson, Rutger Hauer, Max von Sydow, Priya Darshini
   </actor>
	  <about>A drama that explores the life of Mother Teresa through letters she wrote to her longtime friend and spiritual advisor, Father 
	  Celeste van Exem over a nearly 50-year period.</about>
   </film15>
   
   	
	<film16>
      <Film>The Last Night (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 3rd July2014</Date>
	  <actor> Kôji Yakusho, Nana Komatsu, Satoshi Tsumabuki, Hiroya Shimizu
   </actor>
	  <about>As former detective Akikazu searches for his missing daughter, Kanako, he soon learns she has a mysterious secret life.</about>
   </film16>
   
   <film17>
      <Film>The Lego Movie  (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 7th feb 2014</Date>
	  <actor> Chris Pratt, Will Ferrell, Elizabeth Banks
   </actor>
	  <about>An ordinary Lego construction worker, thought to be the prophesied 'Special', is recruited to join a quest to stop an evil 
   tyrant from gluing the Lego universe into eternal stasis.
</about>
   </film17>
   
<film18>
      <Film>Penguins of Madagascar (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 26th November 2014</Date>
	  <actor>Tom McGrath, Chris Miller, Christopher Knights 
   </actor>
	  <about>Skipper, Kowalski, Rico and Private join forces with undercover organization The North Wind to stop the villainous Dr. Octavius Brine
   from destroying the world as we know it.
</about>
  </film18>
   
  <film19>
      <Film>Veronica Mars (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 14th March 2014</Date>
	  <actor>Kristen Bell, Jason Dohring, Enrico Colantoni
   </actor>
	  <about> Years after walking away from her past as a teenage private eye, Veronica Mars gets pulled back to her hometown
   - just in time for her high school reunion - in order to help her old flame Logan Echolls, who's embroiled in a murder mystery.
</about>
   </film19>
   
   
   
  <film20>
      <Film>X-Men: Days of Future Past (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 23rd May 2014</Date>
	  <actor> Patrick Stewart, Ian McKellen, Hugh Jackman 
   </actor>
	  <about> The X-Men send Wolverine to the past in a desperate effort to change history
	  and prevent an event that results in doom for both humans and mutants.
</about>
  </film20>
   
   <film21>
      <Film> The Amazing Spider-Man 2 (2014)</Film>
      <Date> 2nd May 2014</Date>
	  <actor> Andrew Garfield, Emma Stone, Jamie Foxx 
   </actor>
	  <about> When New York is put under siege by Oscorp, it is up to Spider-Man to save the city he swore to protect as well as his loved ones.
</about>
  </film21>
 </year>
 
 
<h2>year2013<h2>
<film22>
      <Film>Man of Steel (2013)</Film>
      <Date> 14 June 2013 </Date>
	  <actor> Henry Cavill, Amy Adams, Michael Shannon
   </actor>
	  <about> Clark Kent, one of the last of an extinguished race disguised as an unremarkable human, is
 forced to reveal his identity when Earth is invaded by an army of survivors who threaten to bring the planet to the brink of destruction.

</about>
   </film22> 
   
   <film23>
      <Film>The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (2013)</Film>
      <Date> 22 November 2013 </Date>
	  <actor> Jennifer Lawrence, Josh Hutcherson, Liam Hemsworth
   </actor>
	  <about> Katniss Everdeen and Peeta Mellark become targets of the Capitol after their victory in the 
	  74th Hunger Games sparks a rebellion in the Districts of Panem.
</about>
   </film23>
   
   <film24>
      <Film>   Frozen (I) (2013)</Film>
      <Date> 22 November 2013 </Date>
	  <actor> Kristen Bell, Idina Menzel, Jonathan Groff
   </actor>
	  <about> When the newly crowned Queen Elsa accidentally uses her power to turn things 
into ice to curse her home in infinite winter, her sister, Anna, teams up with a mountain man, 
his playful reindeer, and a snowman to change the weather condition.

</about>
   </film24>
   

   <film25>
      <Film>  Despicable Me 2 (2013)</Film>
      <Date> 3 July 2013  </Date>
	  <actor> Steve Carell, Kristen Wiig, Benjamin Bratt
   </actor>
	  <about> When Gru, the world's most super-bad turned super-dad has been recruited by a team of
 officials to stop lethal muscle and a host of Gru's own, He has to fight back with new gadgetry, cars, and more minion madness.
</about>
   </film25>

  <film26>
      <Film>   Thor: The Dark World (2013)</Film>
      <Date>  8 November 2013  </Date>
	  <actor> Chris Hemsworth, Natalie Portman, Tom Hiddleston 
   </actor>
	  <about> When Dr Jane Foster gets cursed with a powerful object, Thor must protect it before an army 
and its ruthless leader try to get their hands on it to take over the remains of Earth.

</about>
   </film26> 
   
   <film27>
      <Film>  The Wolverine (2013) </Film>
      <Date>  26 July 2013  </Date>
	  <actor> Hugh Jackman, Will Yun Lee, Tao Okamoto
   </actor>
	  <about>When Wolverine is summoned to Japan by an old acquaintance, he is 
	  embroiled in a conflict that forces him to confront his own demons.
</about>
  </film27>
  
 <film28>
      <Film>  The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug (2013)</Film>
      <Date> 13 December 2013   </Date>
	  <actor> Ian McKellen, Martin Freeman, Richard Armitage
   </actor>
	  <about>The dwarves, along with Bilbo Baggins and Gandalf the Grey, continue their quest to 
reclaim Erebor, their homeland, from Smaug. Bilbo Baggins is in possession of a mysterious and magical ring.

</about>
  </film28>
   
<film29>
      <Film> World War Z (2013)</Film>
      <Date>  21 June 2013  </Date>
	  <actor> Brad Pitt, Mireille Enos, Daniella Kertesz
   </actor>
	  <about>United Nations employee Gerry Lane traverses the world in a race against time to stop
 the Zombie pandemic that is toppling armies and governments, and threatening to destroy humanity itself.
</about>
   </film29>
   
<film30>
      <Film>G.I. Joe: Retaliation (2013)</Film>
      <Date>28 March 2013   </Date>
	  <actor> Dwayne Johnson, Channing Tatum, Adrianne Palicki
   </actor>
	  <about>The G.I. Joes are not only fighting their mortal enemy Cobra; they are forced to contend with threats 
from within the government that jeopardize their very existence.
</about>
   </film30> 
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
 
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   

   
   
   
   
   

   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   

   	



